The vision I want:
One-click deposit.
Let's say
you're sitting on XRP.
You want to deposit into
a USDC vault in Ethereum.
You should just be able to
click
and deposit XRP
and then the rest is
taken care of
by Intents.
There needs to be a
everything one app that
that you can use
everything's onchain
because CEXs
don't cover that.
There is a need for
one app.
But I would say it's like
next-generation savings app
because it's not like Revolut.
Because I think people
like to speculate.
An app should be able to
allow you to do that.
So if I was a person
who had XRP
what would you say to me
to like
just check out MoreMarkets?
XRP is becoming
something like
a currency.
Everything that we hold
is a currency.
So if you've been holding
this thing for
5-6 years
and not earning anything
I think you're losing
2-3%.
That could matter
if you're a big holder.
When people think of
MoreMarkets
they think of:
"This is where I put
my idle assets
to make money?"
Yes.